myvishal.com 2015-06-29

# Vishal Mega Mart India- Our Privacy Policy

### Last update Date: 17th Dec 2014

Vishal E-Commerce Private Limited (“VEPL”) is licensed to use and manage website [www.myvishal.com](http://www.myvishal.com/), [www.myvishal.com/grocery](http://www.myvishal.com/grocery) and [www.myvishal.com/fashion](http://www.myvishal.com/fashion) (“The Site”). [www.myvishal.com](http://www.myvishal.com/) knows that you care for how your information is collected and used.

This Privacy Policy lists the data which is collected by us for using the site and the manner in which it is collected. As a visitor to the site, we recommend that you read this ‘Privacy Policy’ carefully. By accessing the site and its services, you agree and accept the practices described in this policy.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU?

As part of registration process on the Site, VEPL may collect your name, email id, mobile phone; billing and delivery address (es). Some of the details are optional – Gender, Date of Birth. We will collect personally identifiable information (PII) only as part of Registration process which is voluntary. This information is also captured if you place an order using the Site.

PII may also be collected if you participate in any surveys conducted by us or if you submit any feedback on the Site.

We also collect and store non-personally identifiable information related to your interaction with the Site. Like many websites, we use ‘cookies’ to obtain such information. We may collect the pages you visit on the Site, the links you click on the Site, the number of times you access the page and any such browsing information on the Site.

The Site may contain links to other web sites and VEPL is not responsible for privacy policy of such websites which VEPL doesn’t own, control or manage. Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### HOW DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION?

VEPL may use this information to personalized services/features on the site and to improve your shopping experience at the Site. We may use this data for personalized offers through the Site or other channels. VEPL uses this information with its business associates and partners for handling your orders and to get in touch with you, as and when necessary to provide the services requested by you. VEPL will store your transaction history as per governing laws. We may use this information to direct our efforts for improving the Site, services.

### WITH WHOM WILL WE SHARE THIS INFORMATION?

VEPL will not use your financial information except to complete the transaction. VEPL does not share, rent out or sell your personal information or disclose your PI to any third party. In cases you have requested for services using the Site, we may use this information with our partners and business associates where it is necessary to complete the transaction. VEPL may use this information to help investigate, prevent and take action against unlawful or fraudulent activities, violation of the Site’s terms and use. We will share this information under special circumstances like requests by law enforcement agencies. You agree and consent for myvishal.com to disclose your information, if so required under the applicable law.

As in any business, we may acquire new stores or sell our store; the company may get acquired. In such cases, customer information is one of the assets which get transferred. Such information will be made available to you through public announcements or by email communication.

### HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. No Payment related information is stored within this portal and it is totally handled directly with payment gateway.

While we have electronic and process controlled access to your information, Myvishal.com cannot be held responsible for any disclosure of your information by unauthorized access by third party or by errors in transmission.

### POLICY UPDATES

VEPL can amend this policy on time to time on its discretion. Last updated date is available for you to view along with policy. You should check the Site frequently for any changes to this policy.

If you have any questions on this policy, please write to [customerservice@myvishal.com](mailto:customerservice@myvishal.com)
